

# EVGENII KULESHOV

# **QA Engineer**

#Fintech #Retail

## **ABOUT ME**

QA with 5+ years of testing experience in web UI and API, test leading and automation. I'm adaptable, team-oriented, and focused on improving my skills in test automation and QA leadership.



@Kes13



+34 654 745 706



github.com/KuleshovES



es.kuleshov@yahoo.com



Valencia, Spain

# LANGUAGE

0

English (B2)



Russian (Native)



Spain (A1)

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Manual testing
- Auto testing
- · Functional testing
- Rest-Api testing
- UI Testing
- Leadership
- Agile (Scrum/Kanban)
- Test management

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Senior QA Engineer Innotech - Russia, St. Petersburg

Aug 2021 - Jul 2023

Performing tasks to test a web portal and API backend services for a large bank. Distribution and control of testing tasks in the team as a QA Lead.

Middle Test Engineer Kaspersky - Russia, St. Petersburg

Sep 2019 - Jul 2021

Conducting manual testing of the web portal on the user's personal account project (Managing antivirus licenses, devices, etc.)

Middle Test Engineer Raiffeisen Bank - Russia, Omsk

Aug 2018 - Sep 2019

Perform backend manual and automatic testing of all banking product integration processes.

Junior Test Engineer Luxoft - Russia, Omsk

Nov 2017 - Aug 2018

Manual testing of desktop applications for a large retail seller.

### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES**

Bachelor's degree in automated information processing and control systems

Sep 2011 - May 2015

Java Programming (Beginner)

Corporate course RaiffeisenBank - May 2019

Python Programming (Beginner)

Stepik - Oct 2023